Next, you'll practice reading and trying to
بعد ذلك، ستتمرن على القراءة وتحاول فهم
understand Python code that's already been written.
تعليمة Python البرمجية التي تمت كتابتها بالفعل.
Whenever you're programming, you need to think about
في أي وقت تحتاج فيه للبرمجة، تحتاج إلى التفكير
the future readers and maintainers of the code you're writing.
في قراء المستقبل وعمال الصيانة للتعليمة البرمجية التي تكتبها.
In this section, you won't change what the code does,
في هذا القسم، لن تغير ما تفعله التعليمة البرمجية،
but you'll first try to understand it in its current state,
ولكن ستحاول أولاً فهمه في حالته الحالية،
then you'll make it easier to use, read and maintain.
ثم ستسهّل استخدامه وقراءته وصيانته.
Reading and refactoring code are important skills for Python programmer.
تعد مهارات القراءة وإعادة بناء التعليمة البرمجية مهمة لمبرمج Python.
What do you mean by refactoring, Charlie?
ماذا تقصد بإعادة بناء التعليمة البرمجية، تشارلي؟
Factoring is another word for decomposing a complex problem into simpler parts.
بناء التعليمة البرمجية هي كلمة أخرى لتحليل مشكلة معقدة إلى أجزاء أبسط.
You practiced that earlier on the Scores To Rating problem.
لقد مارست ذلك في وقت سابق على مشكلة تصنيف النقاط.
Refactoring just means doing this decomposition process on code that already exists.
إعادة بناء التعليمة البرمجية يعني فقط القيام بعملية التحليل هذه على التعليمة البرمجية الموجودة بالفعل.
It's like reorganizing the workshop.
إنها مثل إعادة تنظيم ورشة العمل.
To work efficiently, you need to tidy up so you can find each tool as you need it.
للعمل بكفاءة، تحتاج إلى إجراء ترتيب بحيث يمكنك العثور على كل أداة حسب احتياجك لها.
In general, keeping you on top of
بشكل عام، سيساعد الاحتفاظ بأعلى ترتيب من التعليمة البرمجية الخاصة بك
the organization of your code will make it easier to maintain.
على تسهيل عملية المحافظة عليها.
You'll thank yourself later.
ستشكر نفسك لاحقًا.